Guide to the Henri Chopin Papers GEN MSS 868
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 1957-2007; 7; 154203; 15.62 Linear Feet (46 boxes) + 3 objects
  - Sound Recordings, 154243
    - Audiocassettes, commercially released and non-commercial, 154271
      - Works by other, unsorted, 154272
        - Maillard, Claude. "Sat. L. Robot", 1993; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:20 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507893)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&7be3a211-fbe1-4936-ad61-129ff63b6a77
        - Maillard, Claude. "Sat. L. Robot", 1993; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:51:37 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); A high amount of hiss can be heard on the tape. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507901)
          This audiocassette appears to be a duplicate. Duration: 52'
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&970a7ba4-e9b8-4ae9-9e29-277ef3012ecb
        - Maillard, Claude. "Mnésis", 1983?; 1 Audiocassettes; 00:55:03 Duration (HH:MM:SS.mmm); The program is distorted at times. (Box 80, Item barcode 39002104507919)
          https://preservica.library.yale.edu/explorer/explorer.html#prop:4&4aea451a-1dfb-456a-9193-360caeb46e6d
    - Non-commercial compact discs, 154251
      Box 72 (sound recordings): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Acquaviva, Frederic. "Henri Chopin: la sonore 1/2" (CDR 16), 2005; 154270 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0004
        - pour henri chopin! henri chopin la sonore par frederic acquaviva 2005 1/2, 2011-genm-47008-0004; 1 CD-Rs; 605480108 bytes 605.48 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Acquaviva, Frederic. "Henri Chopin: la sonore 2/2" (CDR 17), 154269 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0005
        - henri chopin la sonore par frederic acquaviva 2/2, 2011-genm-47008-0005; 1 CD-Rs; 343890668 bytes 343.89 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Barriere, Frangoise. "Ritratto di Faciulla" (CDR 7), 154268 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0006
        - François BARRIERE S99 CG 872 Ritratto di FanciuPa 14'05, 2011-genm-47008-0006; 1 CD-Rs; 150048236 bytes 150.05 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Beuvrote, Olivier. "Sons antarctiques et austraux" (CDR 8), 154267 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0007
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0007; 1 CD-Rs; 221026892 bytes 221.03 Megabytes (Box 72)
      - Chopin / Acquaviva. "Radio Libertaire" (CDR 15), 2007 August 2; 154266 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0008
        - Radio Libertaire H. Chopin F. Acquaviva 8/2/2007, 2011-genm-47008-0008; 1 CD-Rs; 202780076 bytes 202.78 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin / Barras. "Entretien Chopin - Barras 1. Radiophonic" (CDR 12), 2003 November 3; 154265 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0009
        - Entretien Chopin-Barras 7 Radiophon'ic 2003 3 novembre, 2011-genm-47008-0009; 1 CD-Rs; 524145596 bytes 524.15 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin / Gaburo. "Few" (CDR 9), 1985 April 9; 154264 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0010
        - "FEW" CHOPIN/CABURO 9 - IV - 1985 copie d'Ajres' K7 Reoliseê 2u studio ACCEŚ DIGITAL, ROUEN, 2011-genm-47008-0010; 1 CD-Rs; 55815356 bytes 55.82 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin / Yterce. "Frises Majeures de Levres and Clarte" (CDR 4), 1999; 154263 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0011
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0011; 1 CD-Rs; 79408268 bytes 79.41 MBegabytes (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Symphonie du nez et de la bouche" (CDR 2), 2005 January; 154262 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0012
        - Symphonie du nez, 2011-genm-47008-0012; 1 CD-Rs; 296387324 bytes 296.39 Megabytes (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Reliefs sur reliefs pour une vie reelle" (CDR 3), 2005 April; 154261 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0013
        - Henri Chopin - Reliefs sur reliefs… -Souffle bouche, 2011-genm-47008-0013; 1 CD-Rs; 607542812 bytes 607.54 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Dans le silence lance I'air" (CDR 5), 154260 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0014
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0014; 1 CD-Rs; 169127660 bytes 169.13 Megabytes (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "1990 - Lyon - Villa Gillet" (CDR 6), 1995 October; 154259 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0015
        - Henri CHOPIN-- Villa Gillet, Lyon 10/95, 2011-genm-47008-0015; 1 CD-Rs; 153940796 bytes 153.94 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Frises Majeures de Levres / Staccati en Glissendo" (CDR 10), 1994; 154258 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0016
        - H. CHOPIN. I: FRISES MAJEURES DES LEURES. 1994. II STACCATI EN GLISSENDO Paue UNE VOIX., 2011-genm-47008-0016; 1 CD-Rs; 426057788 bytes 426.06 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Radiophonic" (CDR 11), 2003; 154257 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0017
        - Henri Chopin Radiophon'ic 2003, 2011-genm-47008-0017; 1 CD-Rs; 607373468 bytes 607.37 Megabytes (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "Performance. Radiophonic" (CDR 13), 2003 November 2; 154256 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0018
        - Performance Chopin Radiophon'ic 2 novembre 2003, 2011-genm-47008-0018; 1 optical_disks; 656676092 bytes 656.68 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Chopin, Henri. "The body is a sound facory and Co." (CDR 1), undated; 154255 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0019
        - master CHOPIN Le - luxe title: "THE BODY IS A SOUND FACTORY & Co."…, 2011-genm-47008-0019; 1 CD-Rs; 316169996 bytes 316.17 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Pisek et al. "Chopin class October 2004" (CDR 18), 154254 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0020
        - CHOPIN CLASS OCTOBER 2004 7TRACKS AUDIO STEREO B. PISEK 2004, 2011-genm-47008-0020; 1 CD-Rs; 217233116 bytes 217.23 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - "Joncours internationale de poesie sonore. Radiophonic. CD 2" (CDR 14), 2003; 154253 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0021
        - concours international de poésie sonore RADIOPHON'ic 2003 CD 2, 2011-genm-47008-0021; 1 CD-Rs; 542561756 bytes 542.56 Megabytes. (Box 72)
      - Unidentified, undated; 154252 (Box 72)
        Copies of electronic files may be requested through Access Services: Disk # 2011.genm.47008.0022
        - GEORGES ?E?BOH, 2011-genm-47008-0022; 1 CD-Rs; 276931536 bytes 276.93 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 72)
    - Commercially released compact discs, 154244
      Boxes 73-77 and 80 (sound recordings): Use of originals is restricted. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Works by Chopin, unsorted, 154250; (29 compact discs) (Box 73)
        - henri chopin les 9 saintes-phonies, 2011-genm-47008-0030; 1 CD-Rs; 783745244 bytes 783.75 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - De Henri Chopin, le dernier page 3, 2011-genm-47008-0031; 1 DVD-Rs; 3269132288 bytes 3.27 Gigabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 73)
        - HENRY CHOPIN "LA PLAINE DES RESPIRS" TOCHNIT ALEPH 072, 2011-genm-47008-0032; 1 CD-Rs; 633457148 bytes 633.46 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - HENRI CHOPIN "LE FOND DE LA GORGE", 2011-genm-47008-0033; 1 CD-Rs; 100171724 bytes 100.17 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - transparence Hypnopop Unprod 1993, 2011-genm-47008-0034; 1 CD-Rs; 477597164 bytes 477.60 Megabytes (Box 73)
        - Henri CHOPIN Oeuvres artalect A.102, 2011-genm-47008-0035; 1 CD-Rs; 640228556 bytes 640.23 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - HENRI CHOPIN LE CORPSBIS & CO. NEPLESS PS 961 1001, 2011-genm-47008-0036; 1 CD-Rs; 799844684 bytes 799.84 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - Son@rt 022 Henri CHOPIN 1 & 2 Pêche de Nuit (1957) 3 Les souffles des tempêtes (1993) enregistré à Bagnolet le 19 mai 2000 Publié avec le concours du Centre National du Livre A. D. L.M 2001, 2011-genm-47008-0037; 1 CD-Rs; 276632876 bytes 276.63 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - henri chopin sfd-Lectures 92/93, 2011-genm-47008-0038; 1 CD-Rs; 817905692 bytes 817.91 Megabytes (Box 73)
        - Parant pour H. Chopin Images DS Calder + portrait JLP, 2011-genm-47008-0039; 1 CD-Rs; 520201248 bytes 520.20 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 73)
        - henri chopin remixed sound poetry live II, 2011-genm-47008-0040; 1 CD-Rs; 760394588 bytes 760.39 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - henri chopin remixed sound poetry live II, 2011-genm-47008-0041; 1 CD-Rs; 760394588 bytes 760.39 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - artalect la délivrance l'audio contre Henri Chopin Poésie sonore 2003, 2011-genm-47008-0042; 1 CD-Rs; 542441804 bytes 542.44 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - "MELT INTO THE ENVIRONMENT" STEREO 34:30 B.P:sen 03/2004, 2011-genm-47008-0043; 1 optical_disks; 366926156 bytes 366.93 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - Henri CHOPIN Oeuvres artalect A.102, 2011-genm-47008-0044; 1 CD-Rs; 640228556 bytes 640.23 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - transparence Hypnopop Unprod 1993, 2011-genm-47008-0045; 1 CD-Rs; 477597164 bytes 477.60 Megabytes (Box 73)
        - Henri Chopin [autograph], 2011-genm-47008-0046; 1 CD-Rs; 182978588 bytes 182.98 Megabytes (Box 73)
        - HENRI CHOPIN LE CORPSBIS & CO. NEPLESS PS 961 1001, 2011-genm-47008-0047; 1 CD-Rs; 799844684 bytes 799.84 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - ide: [ampf] notes, poems, sequences & songs, 2011-genm-47008-0048; 1 CD-Rs; 782416364 bytes 782.42 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - Henri Chopin Eva Roither Tonspuren 3. und 5. 12. 2004 Mein Körper ist eine Klangfabrik, 2011-genm-47008-0049; 1 CD-Rs; 420055484 bytes 420.06 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - HENRi CHOPiN 14-12-07 AT RADIO CENTRRAAAL! 106.7 FM, 2011-genm-47008-0050; 1 CD-Rs; 710471036 bytes 710.47 Megabytes. (Box 73)
        - Trio d'été - 1979, 2011-genm-47008-0051; 1 CD-Rs; 263790956 bytes 263.79 Megabytes (Box 73)
        - DON'T FOLLOW ME. FOLLOW YOUR LIFE. BRUNO PISEK 2005 FOR HENRI, 2011-genm-47008-0052; 1 CD-Rs; 367481228 bytes 367.48 Megabytes. (Box 73)
      - Works by others, unsorted, 154249; (47 compact discs) (Box 74)
        - [ÅKE HODELL] 1, 2011-genm-47008-0053; 1 CD-Rs; 829924412 bytes 829.92 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [ÅKE HODELL] 2, 2011-genm-47008-0054; 1 CD-Rs; 837347324 bytes 837.35 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [ÅKE HODELL] 3, 2011-genm-47008-0055; 1 CD-Rs; 838417484 bytes 838.42 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - trânsito Local trânsito Vocal SETE PARTITURAS TIPOGRÁFICAS DE JORGE DOS REIS INTERPRETAÇÃO FONÉTICA DE AMÉRICO RODRIGUES E JORGE DOS REIS, 2011-genm-47008-0056; 1 CD-Rs; 429693980 bytes 429.69 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Hervé Brunaux chers amis chers amis (10'59"), 2011-genm-47008-0057; 1 CD-Rs; 116205308 bytes 116.21 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - HUGH DAVIES WARMING UP WITH THE ICEMAN, 2011-genm-47008-0058; 1 CD-Rs; 592447676 bytes 592.45 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - maria faustino danse zygomatique no 9 8/10 la société mobile, 2011-genm-47008-0059; 1 DVD-Rs; 394821632 bytes 394.82 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 74)
        - explorations in sound musicworks GORDON MONAHAN | ELLEN FULLMAN W. MARK SUTHERLAND RICHARD TEITELBAUM | TIM BRADY, 2011-genm-47008-0060; 1 CD-Rs; 779377580 bytes 779.38 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - MIGUEL AZGUIME WORKS, 2011-genm-47008-0061; 1 CD-Rs; 811221308 bytes 811.22 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - DISC 1 OS.002, 2011-genm-47008-0062; 1 CD-Rs; 754095932 bytes 754.10 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - DISC 2 cd-rom part: MFDM by Servo. OS.002, 2011-genm-47008-0063; 1 CD-Rs; 623980940 bytes 623.98 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - KURT SCHWITTERS URSONATE - SONATE DE SONS PRIMITIFS 1921-32 BERNARD HEIDSIECK POEME - PARTITION B2 B3, 1962, 2011-genm-47008-0064; 1 CD-Rs; 78321644 bytes 78.32 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0065; 1 CD-Rs; 577585388 bytes 577.59 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Toc La Fricke Mai 2007, 2011-genm-47008-0066; 1 CD-Rs; 558595340 bytes 558.60 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Flying Swimming fs00001 Total 66:15, 2011-genm-47008-0067; 1 CD-Rs; 704805068 bytes 704.81 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Flying Swimming fs00001 Total 65:29, 2011-genm-47008-0068; 1 CD-Rs; 698774540 bytes 698.77 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Principle Hope Daniel Carter Laurence Cook Peter Kowald Jonathan LaMaster, 2011-genm-47008-0069; 1 CD-Rs; 616598012 bytes 616.60 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - DES PAPIERS!, 2011-genm-47008-0070; 1 DVD-Rs; 100270508 bytes 100.27 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - CD 4 -text-sound-compositions- FLYKINGEN RECORDS, 2011-genm-47008-0071; 1 CD-Rs; 687969452 bytes 687.97 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - CD 3 -text-sound-compositions- FLYKINGEN RECORDS, 2011-genm-47008-0072; 1 CD-Rs; 787515500 bytes 787.52 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - CD 2 -text-sound-compositions- FLYKINGEN RECORDS, 2011-genm-47008-0073; 1 CD-Rs; 765900620 bytes 765.90 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - CD 1 -text-sound-compositions- FLYKINGEN RECORDS, 2011-genm-47008-0074; 1 CD-Rs; 737885948 bytes 737.89 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - CD 5 -text-sound-compositions- FLYKINGEN RECORDS, 2011-genm-47008-0075; 1 CD-Rs; 765794780 bytes 765.79 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Eyes Dance, 2011-genm-47008-0076; 1 optical_disks (Box 74)
        - VOCAL NEIGHBORHOODS Compilation Leonardo 1994 ISAST 3, 2011-genm-47008-0077; 1 CD-Rs; 737100380 bytes 737.10 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - HERMANN NITSCH Sinfonia Punta Campanella in 4 movimenti, 2011-genm-47008-0078; 1 CD-Rs; 668953532 bytes 668.95 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - The Pioneers FIVE TEXT-SOUND ARTISTS 1 Lars-Gunnar Bodin Ilmar Laaban Sten Hanson, 2011-genm-47008-0079; 1 CD-Rs; 765451388 bytes 765.45 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - The Pioneers FIVE TEXT-SOUND ARTISTS 2 Sten Hanson Åke Hodell Bengt Emil Johnson, 2011-genm-47008-0080; 1 CD-Rs; 765957068 bytes 765.96 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0081; 1 CD-Rs; 774527756 bytes 774.53 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0082; 1 CD-Rs; 801312332 bytes 801.31 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0083; 1 CD-Rs; 808528268 bytes 808.53 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - JAAP D7ONK KONSTRANS 947 AV3RSCHUW © DUMA / ST3MRA, 2011-genm-47008-0084; 1 CD-Rs; 559086908 bytes 559.09 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0085; 1 CD-Rs; 22739136 bytes 22.74 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 74)
        - Photographies Directeurs Imeb, 2011-genm-47008-0086; 1 CD-Rs; 2384928 bytes 2.38 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 74)
        - Ploto (PSD) Jacques DONGUY 1998 - Reme Parlée - Centre POMPiDOU, 2011-genm-47008-0087; 1 CD-Rs; 46202688 bytes 46.20 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 74)
        - IDE AMPF, 2011-genm-47008-0088; 1 CD-Rs; 772566188 bytes 772.57 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - [kwad] live on Kinesonus 16.5.04, 2011-genm-47008-0089; 1 CD-Rs; 188543420 bytes 188.54 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - B. Ferrando A. Saavedra, 2011-genm-47008-0090; 1 DVD-Rs; 1759084544 bytes 1.76 Gigabytes This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 74)
        - bruno pisek 10/2007 1 text 1 foto B. Pisek, 2011-genm-47008-0091; 1 CD-Rs; 2050944 bytes 2.05 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 74)
        - Chopin les Tomeaux, 2011-genm-47008-0092; 1 CD-Rs; 419441612 bytes 419.44 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Demo Mulberry Hawk May 2005, 2011-genm-47008-0093; 1 CD-Rs; 255817676 bytes 255.82 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - 1 FLEDERMÄUSE 27 europäische Arten Echtzeit (Mischerdetektor), 2011-genm-47008-0094; 1 CD-Rs; 650567948 bytes 650.57 Megabytes. (Box 74)
        - Licences No I FEW Kenneth GABRUO - Henri CHOPIN II LE FOND DE LA GORGE Henri Chopin III CRESCENDO AUX VOCEMES Henri CHOPIN IV EST-QUEST François DUFRÊNE V INTENSITES Alexandre YTERCE VI FRISES MAJEURES DES LEVRES + CLARTE Henri CHOPIN - Alexandre YTERCE November 1999, 2011-genm-47008-0095; 1 CD-Rs; 483393536 bytes 483.39 Megabytes. (Box 74)
      - Works by others, unsorted, 154248; (29 compact discs) (Box 75)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0096; 1 CD-Rs; 307787424 bytes 307.79 Megabytes. This reflects the size of the carrier media, but may not accurately reflect the extent of digital files available for research. (Box 75)
        - JACQUES DONGUY TAG-SURFUSION avec la collaboration de Ramuntcho Matta A.D.L.M. SonArt 001, 2011-genm-47008-0097; 1 CD-Rs; 503560892 bytes 503.56 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - SATIE.TATI.KAKI FRACTAL MUSIC No 1, 2011-genm-47008-0098; 1 CD-Rs; 741373964 bytes 741.37 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Marc Battier Music from the Voice 1999 # 2 One 2 One by M.A.A.T Los Ojos del Amor Voice and paintings by Matta, 2011-genm-47008-0099; 1 CD-Rs; 116661596 bytes 116.66 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - …BOBEOBI LAUTPOESIE GSV Gertraud Scholz Verlag, 2011-genm-47008-0100; 1 CD-Rs (Box 75)
        - DRAMAPHONIE II ALEXANDRE YTERCE JE ME SUIS ARME CONTRE LA JUSTICE, 2011-genm-47008-0101; 1 CD-Rs; 659159804 bytes 659.16 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - ALTAGOR 1 - Conférence, 1950 2-3 - Discours Absolu, extraits, 1960 4-5-6 - Entretien, 1979 A.D.L.M., SonArt 013 Publié avec le concours du Centre National du Livre, 2011-genm-47008-0102; 1 CD-Rs; 742914524 bytes 742.91 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Pierre Henry La Ville. Die Stadt Metropolis Paris Ars Acustica Vom Reichtum der akustischen Kunst, 2011-genm-47008-0103; 1 CD-Rs; 697356284 bytes 697.36 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - THE MACHINE FOR MAKING SENSE TALL POPPIES on second thoughts intimacy on a shelf 1994, 2011-genm-47008-0104; 1 CD-Rs; 678862508 bytes 678.86 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - mfms consciousness, 2011-genm-47008-0105; 1 CD-Rs; 621116204 bytes 621.12 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Les machines animales OHM éditions, 2011-genm-47008-0106; 1 CD-Rs; 336884060 bytes 336.88 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - The Listening Room DELTA various, 2011-genm-47008-0107; 1 CD-Rs; 673201244 bytes 673.20 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - The Listening Room DELTA various, 2011-genm-47008-0108; 1 CD-Rs; 673201244 bytes 673.20 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - [I/T SELECTED POEMS Amanda Stewart], 2011-genm-47008-0109; 1 CD-Rs; 695392364 bytes 695.39 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Invasion of the Night Music from Matta's paintings music by Marc Battier Pre-Production Copy, 2011-genm-47008-0110; 1 CD-Rs; 477521900 bytes 477.52 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - PEACE Ka, 2011-genm-47008-0111; 1 CD-Rs; 81376892 bytes 81.38 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Fractal Musik no 2: "OPÉRETTE D'ARTISTES" Station Mir 1998, 2011-genm-47008-0112; 1 CD-Rs; 749725916 bytes 749.73 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - PHONO SUECIA STEN HANSON JOHN CARTER SONG BOOK, 2011-genm-47008-0113; 1 CD-Rs; 504193580 bytes 504.19 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - ETANT DONNES AURORE 1990 TOUCH, 2011-genm-47008-0114; 1 CD-Rs; 477220844 bytes 477.22 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - stv asm vincent barras jacques demierre 2000, 2011-genm-47008-0115; 1 CD-Rs; 491309324 bytes 491.31 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - ELETTRO CABARET, 2011-genm-47008-0116; 1 CD-Rs; 551137148 bytes 551.14 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - ramuntcho matta 2 l'amour 1993, 2011-genm-47008-0119; 1 CD-Rs; 620438828 bytes 620.44 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Millenium International Revue Son@rt, 2011-genm-47008-0120; 1 CD-Rs; 712935932 bytes 712.94 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - CHRISTIAN CALON Ligne de vie récits électriques, 2011-genm-47008-0121; 1 CD-Rs; 826057724 bytes 826.06 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Frédéric Acquaviva sens unique(s), hörspiel 1996 Casus Belli, 2011-genm-47008-0122; 1 CD-Rs; 627934652 bytes 627.93 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - AL HANSEN ANDY WARHOL ATTENTAT SOUND ? Records, 4, 2001 www.hundertmark-gallery.com, 2011-genm-47008-0123; 1 CD-Rs; 119399324 bytes 119.40 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Est-ce que le son est bon?, 2011-genm-47008-0124; 1 CD-Rs; 616165244 bytes 616.17 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Est-ce que le son est bon?, 2011-genm-47008-0125; 1 CD-Rs; 616165244 bytes 616.17 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Est-ce que le son est bon?, 2011-genm-47008-0126; 1 CD-Rs; 616165244 bytes 616.17 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Alain DE FILIPPIS TON DIEU NE S'APPELLE-T-IL PAS EGO?, 2011-genm-47008-0127; 1 CD-Rs; 162386828 bytes 162.39 Megabytes. (Box 75)
        - Lionel MARCHETTI MUE, 2011-genm-47008-0128; 1 CD-Rs; 221410268 bytes 221.41 Megabytes. (Box 75)
      - Works by others, unsorted, 154247; (29 compact discs) (Box 76)
        - Gerhard Rühm Ophelia and the Words Wald, ein deutsches Requiem Kleine Geschichte der Zivilisation Ars Acustica, 2011-genm-47008-0155; 1 CD-Rs; 765164444 bytes 765.16 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - Le Sacre Du Printemps, 2011-genm-47008-0156; 1 CD-Rs; 746729468 bytes 746.73 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0157; 1 CD-Rs; 745290044 bytes 745.29 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - Fortner Anderson Six Silk Purses, 2011-genm-47008-0158; 1 CD-Rs; 52491956 bytes 52.49 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - jaap blonk, 2011-genm-47008-0159; 1 CD-Rs; 646416668 bytes 646.42 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - A Gherban Ro fractal, 2011-genm-47008-0160; 1 CD-Rs; 102667196 bytes 102.67 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - A Gherban POESIE DIGITALE, 2011-genm-47008-0161; 1 CD-Rs; 398988620 bytes 398.99 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0162; 1 CD-Rs; 152992940 bytes 152.99 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - runzelstirn & gurgelstock 23 brutal-humouroid dramas by Rudolf Eb.er, 2011-genm-47008-0163; 1 CD-Rs; 656335052 bytes 656.34 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - [no label information], 2011-genm-47008-0164; 1 CD-Rs; 47084 bytes 47.08 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - MADE TO MEASURE hom(m)age BRION DYSIN "self-portrait jumping", 2011-genm-47008-0165; 1 CD-Rs; 733640588 bytes 733.64 Megabytes. (Box 76)
        - HERMANN NITSCH 7. SINFONIE 1. TEIL © ? Records, 02, 2000 www.hundertmark-gallery.com, 2011-genm-47008-0166; 1 CD-Rs; 617988044 bytes 617.99 Megabytes. (Box 76)